University of Arizona Office of the President records, 1937-1947
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Allumni Association. 1937-1947 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Allumni Association. 1937-1947 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Allumni Association: Achevement and service awards. 1937-1947 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Appointment Office: Austin Repp and Victot H. Kelley. 1937-1947 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Appointment Office: National Youth Administration correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Buildings and Grounds: Superintendent William J. Bray, miscellaneous correspondence, includes letter of June 18, 1942 recommending purchase of bicycle racks and letter of July 7, 1944 regarding waste paper salvage. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Buildings and Grounds: Budget. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Buildings and Grounds: Personnel and wages. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Buildings and Grounds: Automobiles: Parking. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Buildings and Grounds: Automobiles: Traffic problems. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Buildings and Grounds: Automobiles: Use of. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Buildings and Grounds: Bird cage. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Buildings and Grounds: Bulletin boards; handbills and advertising. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Buildings and Grounds: Cactus Garden. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Buildings and Grounds: Campus Grounds; lawns, walks, trees, lighting, etc. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Buildings and Grounds: Coolers and air conditioning. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Buildings and Grounds: Mail Services. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Buildings and Grounds: Police. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Buildings and Grounds: Smoking problems. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Buildings and Grounds: Telephonr service. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Buildings and Grounds: Utilities; gas, light, water, etc. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Buildings and Grounds: Land and property: Off campus problems. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  Includes correspondence regarding the polo field, zoning ordinances, city lights, proposed commercial establishments on Park Avenue such as; Safeway Store, theater, and Valley National Bank branch, and renovation of Blake house.
- Buildings and Grounds: Farms. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Buildings and Grounds: Saguaro National Monument. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Buildings and Grounds: University Indian Ruins. 1937-1947 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Auditorium and equipment. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Chemisty-Physics building. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Dormitories, new and old Pima Hall. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Various dormitories. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Fine Arts and Herring Hall. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Gymnasium. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Law building, formarly Library. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Mines and Engineering Building. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Old Main. Includes proposal to demolish Old Main as a W.P.A. Project, using salvaged material in the constuction of a new poultry plant. 1939-1941 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: President's House. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Swiming Pools. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Women's Building. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Buildings, use of and alterations to: Miscellaneous Buildings, etc. 1937-1947 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  Includes Administration Building, Mechanic Arts Building, Storage Warehouse, removal of the radio tower (1939), and historical information regarding old shops and the Mines and Engineering Building.
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Douglas Memorial Building for Mines and Metallurgy. 1937-1943 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Douglas Memorial Building for Mines and Metallurgy. 1937-1943 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Douglas Memorial Building for Mines and Metallurgy, Bronze Tablet. 1937-1947 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Dormitory Units (Hopi and Papago) and Stadium extension. 1946-1947 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Yavapai Hall. 1941-1946 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Post War building plan proposals. Includes material regarding Stewart "tent house" on 4th St., built in 1909, and used by the School of Home Economics. 1943-1944 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Post War building plan proposals. Includes material regarding Stewart "tent house" on 4th St., built in 1909, and used by the School of Home Economics. 1943-1944 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Post War buliding plan inquiries regarding sale of bonds. 1945 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Arizona Pioneers' Historical Society Building. 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Student Union Memorial Building. 1938-1947 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: Proposed tennis courts. 1937-1947 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Buildings, construction of; proposed: U.S. Bureau of Mines Buildings. 1945-1947 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Buildings, Federal Works Agency: Public Work Reserve proposed projects. 1941-1942 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Buildings, Federal Works Agency: W.P.A. Campus Improvements. 1937-1940 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Buildings, Federal Works Agency: W.P.A. miscellaneous correspondence and projects. 1937-1942 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Buildings, Federal Works Agency: W.P.A. proposed transfer of poultry farm. 1939-1941 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Buildings, Federal Works Agency: W.P.A. statewide archival & records project. 1938-1942 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Buildings, Federal Works Agency: Bureau of Community Facilities - proposed dormitories. 1945-1947 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Buildings, Federal Works Agency: Bureau of Community Facilities - proposed dormitories. 1945-1947 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Buildings, Federal Works Agency: Bureau of Community Faclities - Veterans' Educational Facilities project 2-V-3. 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Buildings, Federal Works Agency: Bureau of Community Faclities - Veterans' Educational Facilities project 2-V-3. 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Buildings, Federal Public Housing Authority: Polo Villiage. 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Buildings, Federal Public Housing Authority: Polo Villiage. 1946-1947 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- University Committees: Artist Series (formerly Concert and Lecture Series). Includes Comptroller's correspondence. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- University Committees: Assemblies. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- University Committees: Athletics. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- University Committees: Renting of Auditorium and Stadium. Chieftly concerning the Auditorium, but includes also Herring Hall and the "Aggie Auditorium. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- University Committees: Campus. Mostly relating to parking, trees, and srubs. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- University Committees: Catalog. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- University Committees: Rrecommended catalog changes. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- University Committees: Chamber lectures. Includes 1943 correspondence with Margaret Sanger Slee. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- University Committees: Co-ordinating Committe known as the Educational Committee, 1937-1938. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- University Committees: Educational problems/policy. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- University Committees: Educational problems/policy report on Student Living and Study Conditions at UA by E.G. Wood. 1942 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- University Committees: English proficiency. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- University Committees: Extension. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- University Committees: Faculty constitution. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- University Committees: Faculty dining room. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- University Committees: Folklore. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- University Committees: Foreign students. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- University Committees: Freeman Medals. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- University Committees: Freshman Week. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- University Committees: Future development of the University of Arizona. 1937-1947 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- University Committees: Investigation of Nurses' Training Schools' Credits. 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- University Committees: Investigation of Nurses' Training Schools' Credits. 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- University Committees: Library. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- University Committees: National Emergeny Committee. Inventory of personnel and reseach facilities at the UA. 1940 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- University Committees: Patents. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- University Committees: Publications. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- University Committees: Publications. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- University Committees: Publications. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- University Committees: Publications. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- University Committees: Publications. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- University Committees: Publications. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- University Committees: Publications; manuscripts by Estelle Lutrell. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- University Committees: Radio. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- University Committees: Religious Courses. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  Includes President Atkinson's correspondence with various members of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints and courses at the Institute of Religion in Tucson.
- University Committees: Research. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- University Committees: Residence Standing. 1937-1947 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- University Committees: Residence Standing, Arthur Winard Case. 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- University Committees: Retirement. Includes President Atkinson's correspondence with presidents of other universities regarding retirement policies. 1944 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- University Committees: Schedule and rooms. Use of rooms and offices. Includes problems of washrooms and offices (Fitz-Gerald & Lockwood) ib Library. 1938-1943 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- University Committees: Schedule and rooms. Use of rooms and offices. Includes problems of washrooms and offices (Fitz-Gerald & Lockwood) ib Library. 1938-1943 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- University Committees: General Scholarships and Awards. Includes Peterman Award, Rhodes Scholarships, Poetry Awards, Lewis W. Douglas Scholarship, Schmier History Award. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- University Committees: General Scholarships and Awards. Includes Peterman Award, Rhodes Scholarships, Poetry Awards, Lewis W. Douglas Scholarship, Schmier History Award. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- University Committees: Scholarships and Awards for Women. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- University Committees: Scholarships and Awards for Fireign Students. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- University Committees: Small class enrollments. 1942 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- University Committees: Special Occasions. Includes correspondence regarding Commencement location and procedures. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- University Committees: Stadium. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- University Committees: Student Activities. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- University Committees: Student Aid. Includes Freeman Scholarships. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- University Committees: Student reports and examinations. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- University Committees: Student Rodeo. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- University Committees: Surplus war material. 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- University Committees: Univerisity and Soldier's recreation. 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- University Committees: University Forum, formerly Student Forum. Includes Religious Emphasis Week. 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- University Committees: University Forum, formerly Student Forum. Includes Religious Emphasis Week. 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- University Committees: University Motion Pictures. 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- University Committees: War activities. Includes material regarding air raid instructions and first aid kits. 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- University Committees: Miscellaneous Committees. 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- University Committees: Miscellaneous Committees. 1937-1947 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Students: Parental Pleas and Protests. 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Students: Parental Pleas and Protests. 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Students: Parental Pleas and Protests. 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Students: Miscellaneous and general letters to parents. 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Students: Prospective. 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Students: Correspondence with officers, etc. of the Associated Students, Associated Women Students. 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Students: Miscellaneous correspondence with and about. 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Students: General and miscellaneous correspondence with and about after UA Career. 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Students: Various individual correspondence with students after UA career. 1937-1947 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Students: Letters of recommendation. 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Students: Letters of recommendation. 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Students: Publications; Arizona Wildcat, Desert yearbook, and Kitty-Kat. 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Students: National Student Organizations; World Student Service Fund and National Student Federation of America. 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Students: Ellinwood vocabulary contest. 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Students: Fraternitieis and Sororities. 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Students: Fraternities and Sororities, loans from the Timber Fund. 1937-1947 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- World War II: Naval Training School. 1942-1946 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- World War II: Naval Training School. 1942-1946 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- World War II: Naval Training School. 1942-1946 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- World War II: Naval Training School. 1942-1946 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- World War II: Naval Training School. Adjustments in the use of UA facilities. Includes correspondence with W.J. Bray and J.F. McKale. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- World War II: Naval Training School. Adjustments in the use of UA facilities. Includes correspondence with W.J. Bray and J.F. McKale. (Box 28, Folder 6)
- World War II: Naval Training School. Financial Records. (Box 28, Folder 7)
- World War II: Naval Training School. Lecture schedules. (Box 28, Folder 8)
- World War II: Navy V-1 Program. Machinists and Electricians' Mates. 1942 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- World War II: Civil Aeronautics Administration War Training Service (Navy Pilots). 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- World War II: Civil Aeronautics Administration War Training Service (Navy Pilots). 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- World War II: Civil Aeronautics Administration War Training Service (Navy Pilots). 1943-1944 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- World War II: Engineering Defence Training Courses. 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- World War II: Engineering Defence Training Courses. 1940-1941 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- World War II: Engineering Defense/War Training Courses. 1942-1945 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- World War II: Army Specialized Training Program. 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- World War II: Army Specialized Training Program. 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- World War II: Army Specialized Training Program. 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- World War II: Army Specialized Training Program. 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- World War II: Army Specialized Training Program. 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- World War II: National Defense Courses. Farm machinery. 1941-1942 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- World War II: Civil Aeronautics Authority: Air Pilot Training. Civilian. 1939-1942 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- World War II: Civil Aeronautics Authority: Air Pilot Training. Civilian. 1939-1942 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- World War II: Civil Aeronautics Authority: Air Pilot Training. UA Committe. 1937-1947 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- World War II: Selective Service System. Misc. and General. 1937-1947 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- World War II: Selective Service System. Faculty A - Z. 1937-1947 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- World War II: Selective Service System. Faculty A - Z. 1937-1947 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- World War II: Selective Service System. Faculty A - Z. 1937-1947 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- World War II: Selective Service System. Students. 1937-1947 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- World War II: Selective Service System. Students. 1937-1947 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- World War II: Veterans Administration. Rehabilitation Training. 1943-1947 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- World War II: Veterans Administration. Rehabilitation Training. 1943-1947 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- World War II: Veterans Administration. Rehabilitation Training. 1943-1947 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- World War II: Veterans Post War Education. 1937-1947 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- World War II: Veterans Housing. 1937-1947 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- World War II: Arizona War Finance Committee. 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- World War II: Civilian Defence Coordinating Council, Arizona Civilian Defense Council, etc. 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- World War II: Commission on College Problems in relation National Defense. 1941-1943 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- World War II: Commission on College Problems in relation National Defense. 1941-1943 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- World War II: Joint Army-Navy-Marine Corps-Coast Guard College Procurement Committee. 1942-1943 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- World War II: Navy College Training Program Selection Committee (v-12 candidates). 1943-1944 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- World War II: Victory Book Campaign. Sponsored by the American Library Association. 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- World War II: Miscellaneous material. 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- World War II: UA War Service Honor Roll (letters accompanying certificates). 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- World War II: National Defense. 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  Includes various committees such as: Committee to Defend American by Aiding the Allies, 1940; National Commitee on Education and Defense, 1940-1941; Office of Civilian Defense, 1941-1942; Citisens Emergency Committee on Non-defense Expensitures, 1941-1942; National War Labor Board, 1943.
- World War II: Japansese-Americans. Miscellaneous correspondence and material. 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- World War II: Japanese-Americans. Proposed UA Extension courses at Internment Camps. Includes correspondence and publicity regarding President Atkinson's statements. 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- World War II: Japanese-Americans. Proposed UA Extension courses at Internment Camps. Includes correspondence and publicity regarding President Atkinson's statements. 1937-1947 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Arizona Peace Officers' Training School. 1939 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Art Matters, miscellaneous. 1937-1947 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Broadman War Library. 1939-1945 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Carnegie Desert Labortory. 1939-1940 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Coolideg Dam Model, shipment from Washington D.C. 1937-1938 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Enterance requirements from High Schools. 1937 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Proposed Federal Research Laboratory. Includes letter from Secertary of Agriculture Henry A. Wallace. 1938 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Gifts. Carnegie Corporation of New York fine art materials. 1938-1943 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Gifts. Mrs. T. Armstrong Jr, file of the London Times. 1943-1944 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Proposed UA Affiliation with Grunou Memorial Clinic, Phoenix. 1939 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Proposed Honorary Degrees. 1941 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Husband and Wife Employment at UA. The Smith/Caldwell Case. 1939 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Proposed Medical School. 1937-1947 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Minimum Wage Cases. 1937-1939 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Union Complaint regarding motion picture operators. Includes letter from Govenor R. C. Stanford. 1937-1938 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Nursing Education. 1942-1944 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Miscellaneous religious matters. 1937-1947 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Salary Increases. 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Miscellaneous scholarships. Includes President's High School Scholarship and Cup Citizens' Military Training Camp Scholarships. 1937-1947 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Proposed School of Social Work. 1940, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Wage Scales. 1937-1947 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Wage Scales. 1937-1947 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Topics A - Z: Wildlife research project with Arizona Game and Fish Commission. 1939-1941 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Latin American Relations: General. Includes correspondence regarding Mexican TV. 1941 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Latin American Relations: General. Includes correspondence regarding Mexican TV. 1941 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Latin American Relations: Universidad de Sonora, Hermosillo, Sonora, Mexico. 1937-1947 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Latin American Relations: Conference on Inter-American relations in the field of education, Washington D.C. October 1939-November 1939 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Latin American Relations: Exchange of students, faculty, scholars. 1937-1947 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Latin American Relations: Exchange of students, faculty, scholars with the Universidad Nacion de Cuyo, Mendoza, Argentina. 1941 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Latin American Relations: Exchange of students, faculty, scholars with the Universidad Nacion de Cuyo, Mendoza, Argentina. 1941 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker President J.F. Zimmerman, University of New Mexico. 1938 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker Albert B. Peterman, includes correspondence with Lewis W. Douglas declining to speak. 1939 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker Lewis W. Douglas. 1940 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker James P. Boyle. 1941 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker President Alfred Atkinson. 1942 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker Richard Pattee, includes correspondence with Robert G. Sproul declining invitation to speak. 1943 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker President Robert G. Sproul, University of California, Berkeley. 1944 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker Rufus B. von KlienSmid, University of Southern California. Includes correspondence with John Foster Dulles declining to speak. 1945 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker President C.A. Dykstra, University of California, Los Angeles. 1946 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Events: Commencement. Speaker T.V. Smith. 1947 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Events: Coranado Cuarto Centennial Celebration. 1939-1940 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Events: Dedication to the Douglas Memorial Building for Mines and Metallurgy. May 27, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  Includes correspondence with Lewis W. Douglas, Walter Douglas, and various other members of the Douglas family; also L.Sl Cates, P.G. Beckett, and H.M Lavender of the Phelp Dodge Corporation.
- Events: Dedication to the Douglas Memorial Building for Mines and Metallurgy. May 27, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 13)